Just checking in to find out if you guys have subscribed to my YouTube, Amanda Seals TV.
You know, I talk a lot about being an independent creative and really doing my due diligence to create like these spaces where I can do like what I want to do.
And then give you all just other options of content, right?
Today, the writer's strikes began and I really genuinely feel like so much of the reason why the writer's strike is happening is because creatives are simply just not being regarded.
And the corporations and the executives are the ones getting paid the most when the creatives are basically over here like scraping and scratching.
So support this creative and you can even do it for free simply just by subscribing to YouTube, Amanda Seals TV.
We're trying to get to 100,000 subscribers by May.
Will you help us? I mean, by the end of May, will you help us do it?
Start today.
Infomercial.